startupli.st 2016-03-08

# StartupLi.st • Find. Follow. Recommend startups.

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you join StartupLi.st 

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used to personalize your experience, to improve our website, and to send periodic email notifications. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

**Third Party Connections**  
We may request connection to third party services such as Twitter, Facebook, and others. StartupLi.st will not modify any third party service data without your direct action. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

**Information disclosure**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. All users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Settings' page. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Terms of Use**  
Please also visit our Terms section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. 

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 4/28/2011
